themusiczoo.com 2019-12-17

# Privacy policy

Return to Homepage

Thank you for visiting our site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at www.themusiczoo.com. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

Collection of Information We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists. Unsubscribing from our newsletter can easily be accomplished by clicking "unsubscribe" in the email, or by contacting us.

Cookie/Tracking Technology The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

Distribution of Information We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes. We will not sell your information to any other entity for 3rd party marketing or any other reason.

Commitment to Data Security Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.

We strive for compliance with, the EU-US Privacy Shield Principles, EU-GDPR principles and the Swiss-US Privacy Shield Principles (the “Privacy Shield Principles”) regarding the collection, use, sharing, and retention of personal information from the European Union and Switzerland.

Personal Information   
You are free to refuse our request for your personal information, with the understanding that we may be unable to process your order without this information. We do not sell your private information to outside parties.   
Personal information we collect   
Personal information comes to us in many different ways, such as:   
• Purchase a product from us   
• Register on the website   
• Submit questions   
• Email us   
• Submit pricing requests on the checkout page   
• Enter a drawing or contest.

Personal data we may collect (if applicable) includes the following:   
• Name   
• Gender   
• Username   
• Password   
• Email address   
• Postal address   
• Phone number and/or mobile number   
• Products viewed or purchased   
Your credit card number, cvv, etc, is held securely by our credit card processor which cannot be accessed by The Music Zoo.

Important – why do I have to accept the terms of this privacy policy?   
This Privacy Policy provides you with all information necessary (in an easily accessible way) to make an informed choice as to whether to use this website and to send your personal information to us or not. Therefore, by browsing this website and communicating electronically with us, you acknowledge and agree to our Processing of your indirect personal information (cookies, connection, and system information) in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy. If you wish to register on the website or ask us to provide a service to you (i.e., a product purchase, newsletter or new product details, etc.) we will need additional direct personal information (e.g., name, address and email address) from you. If you are under [16], we ask you to contact your parent or legal guardian, for your express consent to collect and use this Personal Information. This Personal Information will be used only for the purposes for which you gave it to us.

Privacy Contact Information If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

By e-mail: sales@themusiczoo.com By Phone: 516-626-9292 We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted here.

Return to Homepage

Opens external website in a new window.  Opens in a new window.  Opens external website.  Customer information - The Music Zoo - Checkout
